Harding Black collection, Inclusive: 1910-2014, undated, Bulk: 1954-1998, undated
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
Harding Black collection
Inclusive: 1910-2014, undated, Bulk: 1954-1998, undated
Baylor University, The Texas Collection http://www.baylor.edu/lib/texas/
3911
Black, Harding; Baylor University Development Office; McCoy, Paul
13 document boxes and 3 oversized boxes.
The Harding Black collection contains material on the life, legacy, and career of noted ceramic expert Harding Black. Harding Black's greatest contribution to the ceramics community was his glaze research, which included extensive work to recreate ancient Chinese glazes from the Song and Tang dynasties.
Administrative Information
Physical Description
General condition: Average.
Biography/Profile
Harding Black was born in 1912, near Aransas Pass, Texas. He became interested in ceramics while excavating ancient American Indian mounds near Big Bend, Texas, and was taught to throw clay by his colleague, Rudolf Staffel.
In 1933, Black set up his first studio in a streetcar, behind the Witte Museum, in San Antonio. He taught ceramics classes for children as part of the Witte Museum's series of children's classes. In the late 1930s, Black became involved with the Works Progress Administration (WPA). During the 1940s and 1950s, his work began to be exhibited in major venues, and in 1953, his groundbreaking work on copper-red glazes was featured the January issue of Ceramics Monthly.
Harding Black is best known for his glaze research, primarily in ancient Chinese and Scandinavian glazes. He kept meticulous records of his glaze tests, and it is possible to match the glaze codes found on many of his ceramic test pieces to glaze formulas recorded in his notebooks. As noted in the 1998 exhibition catalog from the University of Dallas, “His discovery of methods which duplicate the elusive chun, flambe, oxblood, and oilspot glazes of ancient China’s Ming and [Song] dynasties fundamentally altered the landscape of contemporary American ceramics.”
In 1989 Harding Black became acquainted with Baylor University ceramist Paul McCoy. The two artists developed a friendship that lasted the rest of Black's life. In 1995, Harding Black gave Baylor University his extensive collection of glaze research, in the form of thousands of test tiles, vases, and bowls, as well as volumes of glaze formulas and related notes.
Harding Black’s work continued to be exhibited and published into the early 2000s, including a retrospective at Baylor University in 1995. Harding Black died of respiratory failure on May 2, 2004.
Scope and Content
The Harding Black collection begins in 1910 and ends in 2014. The bulk of the materials are from 1954-1998. Both Subgroup I. Personal Papers and Subgroup II. Collected Papers are about the same size.
Subgroup I. Personal Papers includes Harding Black's glaze notebooks, firing logs, and other materials he created in his workshop. The most fragile of these materials have been digitized and the papers copies are restricted due to preservation concerns.
Subgroup II. Collected Papers includes materials created by the Curator of the Harding Black Collection and Archive, Professor Paul McCoy, as well as documents from the Baylor University Office of University Development and several avid Harding Black collectors.
Arrangement
Prior to current processing, around half of the collection was in folders with titles and some arrangement. The majority of the over 500 volumes of books in the collection were transferred to the Texas Collection library or to the Baylor University Art Department. The collection is divided into two subgroups: Subgroup I. Personal Papers and Subgroup II. Collected Papers.
Access Restrictions
This collection is restricted. Please see an archivist for details.
Acquisition Information
Accession No. 3911. Acquired 2014-06-12
Related Resources
Related references
Baylor University. “Baylor and Harding Black.” Harding Black Collection and Archive. Accessed 2015 April 17.
Baylor University. “Chronology.” Harding Black Collection and Archive. Accessed 2015 April 17.
Black, Harding. “Sixty Years of Discovery.” Ceramics Monthly 39, no. 10 (1991 December): 36-41.
McCoy, Paul. Interview by archival describers Amanda Dietz and Josh Garland, 2014 August-2015 May.
Harding Black eulogy. NCECA Conference, Baltimore, Maryland, 2005 March 19. Accessed 2015 April 17.
McCoy, Paul. Selected Pieces from the Baylor University Collection of the work of Ceramist Harding Black, [Waco, TX] 1998.
Index Terms
Subjects (Persons)
Black, Harding, 1912- -- Exhibitions.
Subjects (Organizations)
Baylor University -- History -- 20th century.; Baylor University. Department of Art.; Baylor University. Office of University Development -- History.
Places
San Antonio (Tex.) -- History.
Subjects
Glazes -- Formulae.; Pottery, American -- Texas -- San Antonio -- 20th century.
Genres
Clippings (Books, newspapers, etc.); Correspondence.; Photographs.
- Personal Papers, 1910-2000, undated; 1
  Administrative Information
  Physical Description
  General condition: Poor.
  Biography/Profile
  Subgroup I. Personal Papers contains materials created or collected by Harding Black, including his glaze code formulae, firing logs, as well as correspondence and printed publications. The first 3 boxes of the subgroup have been digitized due to the fragile nature of the materials and are also available through the Baylor University Libraries Digital Collections.
  - Business Ledger [RESTRICTED], 1932 July-1943 August (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Firing Logs [RESTRICTED], 1954-1956 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Firing Logs [RESTRICTED], 1956-1958 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Glaze Formulas: Clay Bodies [RESTRICTED], undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Glaze Formulas: Underglazes [RESTRICTED], undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Glaze Formulas: Miscellaneous Clay Bodies and Porcelain Slips [RESTRICTED], undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Glaze Formulas: Miscellaneous Low-Temperature Glazes, Underglazes, and Stains [RESTRICTED], undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Glaze Formulas: A6-A9, miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Glaze Formulas: H982-H1000, A1-A169 [RESTRICTED], undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Glaze Formulas: A170-A547 [RESTRICTED], undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Glaze Formulas: A743-A937 [RESTRICTED], undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Glaze Formulas: A938-A1000 [RESTRICTED], undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Glaze Formulas: A series out of numeric order [RESTRICTED], undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Glaze Formulas: B153-B322 [RESTRICTED], undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Glaze Formulas: B323-B488 [RESTRICTED], undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Glaze Formulas: B489-B772 [RESTRICTED], undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Glaze Formulas: B773-B1000, C1-C49 [RESTRICTED], undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Glaze Formulas: CR 1-CR212 [RESTRICTED], undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Glaze Formulas: B996, C751, C733, C736, CR54, CR76, C839, C842, C40, H910, C822, C87, C922, H188 [RESTRICTED], undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Glaze Formulas: C50-C436 [RESTRICTED], undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Glaze Formulas: C437-C833 [RESTRICTED], undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Glaze Formulas: C834-C1000, D1-D133 [RESTRICTED], undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Glaze Formulas: D134-D365 [RESTRICTED], undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Glaze Formulas: D366-D609, E1-E19 (Ash/Dribble Glazes) [RESTRICTED], undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Glaze Formulas: E1-E399 [RESTRICTED], undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Glaze Formulas: E400-E726 [RESTRICTED], undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Glaze Formulas: E727-E960 [RESTRICTED], undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Glaze Formulas: F1-F36 [RESTRICTED], undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Glaze Formulas: H1-H201 [RESTRICTED], undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Glaze Formulas: H202-H234 [RESTRICTED], undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Glaze Formulas: H235-H322 [RESTRICTED], undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Glaze Formulas: H323-H402 [RESTRICTED], undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Glaze Formulas: H403-H435 [RESTRICTED], undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Glaze Formulas: H436-H573 [RESTRICTED], undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Glaze Formulas: H574-H700 [RESTRICTED], undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Glaze Formulas: H701-H823 [RESTRICTED], undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Glaze Formulas: H824-H981 [RESTRICTED], undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Slip Colors [RESTRICTED], 1952 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Personal, 1971, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Personal, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Personal, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Personal, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Personal, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Personal, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Personal, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Personal, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Personal, 1993, 1995, 1997, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Professional and University: Glaze Research, 1986-1994, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Professional and University: The Haeger Potteries, Incorporated, 1967-1980, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Professional and University: Baylor University, 1989-1994, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Professional and University, 1971-1985 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Professional and University, 1986-1989 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Professional and University, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Professional and University, 1991-1997, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Financial and Legal Documents, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Publications: Exhibition Catalogs, 1910 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Publications: Exhibition Catalogs, 1931, 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Publications: Exhibition Catalogs, 1939, 1949, 1950, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Publications: Exhibition Catalogs, 1957, circa 1960 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Publications: Exhibition Catalogs, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Publications: Exhibition Catalogs, 1961-1962 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Publications: Exhibition Catalogs, 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Publications: Exhibition Catalogs, 1963-1964, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Publications: Exhibition Catalogs, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Publications: Exhibition Catalogs, 1968, 1973, 1978, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Publications: Exhibition Catalogs, 1982-1983, 1986, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Publications: Exhibition Catalogs, 1990, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Publications: Glaze Research: (1 of 2), undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Publications: Glaze Research: (2 of 2), undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Publications: National Council on Education for the Ceramic Arts, 1986-1995 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Publications: Loose Materials and Inscriptions from Harding Black's books, circa 1950-1990 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Publications: General, 1954, 1970, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Printed Materials: Ceramic Organizations, 1955, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Printed Materials: Ceramic Supplies, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Printed Materials: Collected by Harding Black, 1968, 1986-1992, 2000, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Printed Materials: National Council on Education for the Ceramic Arts, 1990-1991, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Printed Materials: Southwest Craft Center, 1977, 1986, undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Notepad with Sketches, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - "Drying Difficulties and Corrections", undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Scrapbook about Harding Black, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Notebook pages, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Collected Papers, 1953-2014; 2
  General condition: Good.
  Subgroup II. Collected Papers contains materials created or collected by Baylor University and avid Harding Black collectors. The subgroup includes substantial information about Baylor University Professor Paul McCoy's work on the Harding Black Collection and Archive, including correspondence with collectors, plans for development dinners, and proposals for possible use of the collection. The end of the subseries includes photographs of Harding Black's work and of Harding Black himself working in his San Antonio studio. There are also multiple oral histories conducted by Paul McCoy with Harding Black and other collectors.
  Index Terms
  Genres
  Cassette tape; Compact disk (CD); Digital versatile disk (DVD); Photo negative; Photographic print; Video home system (VHS) tapes
  - Biographical Materials: Testimonials regarding Harding Black, 1995, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Biographical Materials: National Council on Education for the Ceramic Arts (Texas Studio Ceramics: 1930-1960), 1998 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Biographical Materials: Newspaper clippings and publications, 1992-2000 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Biographical Materials: Harding Black in his own words, 1994, 2004, undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Biographical Materials, General, undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Biographical Materials: Collected by Tom Turnquist, 1933-1994, undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Biographical Materials: Collected by Tom Turnquist, 1986-1997, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Biographical Materials: General, circa 1985-1999, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Collection: General Correspondence, 1995-1997 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Collection: Correspondence about Exhibitions, 1997-2009 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Collection: Correspondence with Collectors [RESTRICTED], 2001-2009 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Collection: Baylor Letters to Harding Black, 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Collection: Harding Black book, 1996, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Collection: Photographs of Storage, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Collection: Paul McCoy request for funding [RESTRICTED], 2008-2009 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Collection: Inventory [RESTRICTED], 1995-1996, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Collection: Collection Storage and Kiln Dock Closet [RESTRICTED], undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Collection: General [RESTRICTED], 1991-1995, undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Contracts and Correspondence: Harding Black names, contact information, and correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1991-2008, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Contracts and Correspondence: Harding Black Collection correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1992-2014 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Donations: Monetary donations [RESTRICTED], 1998, 2004, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Donations: Ceramic donations [RESTRICTED], 1997-2014 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Donations: Jacobsen Donor [RESTRICTED], 2000-2001 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Harding Black Ceramic Research Center: Publications, circa 1990 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Harding Black Ceramic Research Center: Development material [RESTRICTED], 1995-2001, undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Harding Black Ceramic Research Center: Petroleum Club Dinner, 1995 July-October (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Harding Black Ceramic Research Center: Harding Black Dinner and Follow-Up: (1 of 2), 1995, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Harding Black Ceramic Research Center: Harding Black Dinner and Follow-Up: (2 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1995, undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Harding Black Ceramic Research Center: Working Development file: (1 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1995-1998, undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Harding Black Ceramic Research Center: Working Development file: (2 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1995-1998, undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Harding Black Ceramic Research Center: General: (1 of 3) [RESTRICTED], 1995, undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Harding Black Ceramic Research Center: General: (2 of 3) [RESTRICTED], 1995, undated (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Harding Black Ceramic Research Center: General: (3 of 3) [RESTRICTED], 1995, undated (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Legal: Will, Power of Attorney, and Deed of Gift [RESTRICTED], 1991-1998 (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Martin Museum, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - National Council on Education in the Ceramic Arts: Harding Black catalog and exhibition: (1 of 2), 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - National Council on Education in the Ceramic Arts: Harding Black catalog and exhibition: (2 of 2), 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - National Council on Education in the Ceramic Arts: Fort Worth, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - National Council on Education in the Ceramic Arts: General, 2004-2005 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Publications: Ceramics Monthly, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Publications: Harding Black catalog: (1 of 2), 1990-1991, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Publications: Harding Black catalog: (2 of 2), 1990-1991, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Publications: Mailing list and correspondence, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Publications: General, 1953-1954, 1964, 1974, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Publications: General, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Publications: General, 1987-1995, undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Publications: General, 1991, 1993, undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Drawings by Burt Reese, 1945 (Box 17 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Cynthia Perry Notebook, circa 1939-1943 (Box 17 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Design Scrapbook, 1936 (Box 17 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Design Scrapbook (1 of 2), circa 1940 (Box 17 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Design Scrapbook (2 of 2), circa 1940 (Box 17 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - Design Scrapbook, undated (Box 17 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - Design Scrapbook, undated (Box 17 OVZ, Folder 7)
  - Drawing Scrapbook, undated (Box 17 OVZ, Folder 8)
  - Drawing Scrapbook (1 of 2), undated (Box 17 OVZ, Folder 9)
  - Drawing Scrapbook (2 of 2), undated (Box 17 OVZ, Folder 10)
  - Drawing Scrapbook, Loose Materials (1 of 2), undated (Box 17 OVZ, Folder 11)
  - Drawing Scrapbook, Loose Materials (2 of 2), undated (Box 17 OVZ, Folder 12)
  - Animal Drawing Scrapbook (1 of 2), undated (Box 17 OVZ, Folder 13)
  - Animal Drawing Scrapbook (2 of 2), undated (Box 17 OVZ, Folder 14)
  - Website: General, 2009, undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Website: Correspondence, 2008-2009 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Website: Glaze formulas, 2008 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - General Files: Charles Long, 1994-1998 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - General Files: Robert and Margaret Pace Willson [RESTRICTED], 1995-1997 (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - General Files: Research notes for Thomas Turnquist, 1994, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - General Files: Research photographs, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Photographs: Color separation negatives from exhibition catalogue [RESTRICTED], circa 1990 (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - Photographs: Harding Black in Studio: (1 of 4), circa 1990 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Photographs: Harding Black in Studio: (2 of 4), circa 1990 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Photographs: Harding Black in Studio: (3 of 4), circa 1990 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Photographs: Harding Black in Studio: (4 of 4), circa 1990 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Photographs: Negatives of Harding Black and Studio [RESTRICTED], circa 1990 (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - Photographs: Website images, circa 2008 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Photographs: Collector Jim Frink: (1 of 11), circa 1985-2000 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Photographs: Collector Jim Frink: (2 of 11), circa 1985-2000 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Photographs: Collector Jim Frink: (3 of 11), circa 1985-2000 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Photographs: Collector Jim Frink: (4 of 11), circa 1985-2000 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Photographs: Collector Jim Frink: (5 of 11), circa 1985-2000 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Photographs: Collector Jim Frink: (6 of 11), circa 1985-2000 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Photographs: Collector Jim Frink: (7 of 11), circa 1985-2000 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Photographs: Collector Jim Frink: (8 of 11), circa 1985-2000 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Photographs: Collector Jim Frink: (9 of 11), circa 1985-2000 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Photographs: Collector Jim Frink: (10 of 11), circa 1985-2000 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Photographs: Collector Jim Frink: (11 of 11), circa 1985-2000 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Photographs: Collected by Tom Turnquist: (1 of 5), circa 1980-2000 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Photographs: Collected by Tom Turnquist: (2 of 5), circa 1980-2000 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Photographs: Collected by Tom Turnquist: (3 of 5), circa 1980-2000 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Photographs: Collected by Tom Turnquist: (4 of 5), circa 1980-2000 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Photographs: Collected by Tom Turnquist: (5 of 5), circa 1980-2000 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Photographs: Research negatives for Tom Turnquist [RESTRICTED], 1972-1985, undated (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 7)
  - Photographs: General, 1991-1995, undated (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Photographs: General negatives [RESTRICTED], 1991-1995, undated (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 8)
  - Photographs: Large black and white negatives of Harding Black (property of Baylor University Department of Art) [RESTRICTED], circa 1990 (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 9)
  - Electronic Media: Harding Black Interview, Tape #1, VHS, 1989 April 12 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Electronic Media: Harding Black Interview, Tape #1 *copy*, VHS: (1 of 2), 1989 April 12 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Electronic Media: Harding Black Interview, Tape #1 *copy*, VHS: (2 of 2), 1989 April 12 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Electronic Media: Harding Black Interview, Tape #1, cassette tape, 1989 April 12 (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 8)
  - Electronic Media: Harding Black Interview, Tape #1 Part #1, DVD-R: (1 of 2), 1989 April 12 (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 10)
  - Electronic Media: Harding Black Interview, Tape #1 Part #1, DVD-R: (2 of 2), 1989 April 12 (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 11)
  - Electronic Media: Harding Black Interview, Tape #1 Part #2, DVD-R: (1 of 2), 1989 April 12 (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 12)
  - Electronic Media: Harding Black Interview, Tape #1 Part #2, DVD-R: (2 of 2), 1989 April 12 (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 13)
  - Electronic Media: Harding Black Interview, Tape #2, VHS, 1989 April 12 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Electronic Media: Harding Black Interview, Tape #2 *copy*, VHS: (1 of 2), 1989 April 12 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - Electronic Media: Harding Black Interview, Tape #2 *copy*, VHS: (2 of 2), 1989 April 12 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - Electronic Media: Harding Black Interview, Tape #2, cassette tape, 1989 April 12 (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 9)
  - Electronic Media: Harding Black Interview, Tape #2, DVD-R: (1 of 2), 1989 April 12 (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 14)
  - Electronic Media: Harding Black Interview, Tape #2, DVD-R: (2 of 2), 1989 April 12 (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 15)
  - Electronic Media: Harding Black Broadway Street Studio, VHS, 1989 April 12 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 7)
  - Electronic Media: Harding Black Broadway Street Studio *copy*, VHS, 1989 April 12 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 8)
  - Electronic Media: Harding Black Interview, VHS, 1993 June 8 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 9)
  - Electronic Media: Harding Black Interview *copy*, VHS: (1 of 2), 1993 June 8 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 10)
  - Electronic Media: Harding Black Interview *copy*, VHS: (2 of 2), 1993 June 8 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 11)
  - Electronic Media: Harding Black Interview, DVD-R: (1 of 2), 1993 June 8 (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 16)
  - Electronic Media: Harding Black Interview, DVD-R: (2 of 2), 1993 June 8 (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 17)
  - Electronic Media: Baylor University Harding Black Dinner, VHS, 1995 September 19 (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Electronic Media: Baylor University Harding Black Dinner *copy*, VHS: (1 of 2), 1995 September 19 (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Electronic Media: Baylor University Harding Black Dinner *copy*, VHS: (2 of 2), 1995 September 19 (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Electronic Media: William Daley and Paul Hatgil Interview, VHS, 1995 September 19 (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Electronic Media: William Daley and Paul Hatgil Interview *copy*, VHS: (1 of 2), 1995 September 19 (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - Electronic Media: William Daley and Paul Hatgil Interview *copy*, VHS: (2 of 2), 1995 September 19 (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - Electronic Media: William Daley and Paul Hatgil Interview, DVD-R: (1 of 2), 1995 September 19 (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 18)
  - Electronic Media: William Daley and Paul Hatgil Interview, DVD-R: (2 of 2), 1995 September 19 (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 19)
  - Electronic Media: "Harding Black: An American Treasure," VHS: (1 of 2), 1995 (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 7)